7opp.com 2015-02-25

# Website Privacy Policy |7opp.com

7opp.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time. 

In addition, online visitors who wish to purchase a membership through our Web site must provide their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection. 

All online visitor data collected by 7opp.com is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

**

Children’s Privacy

**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 18, we will delete that information from our systems. 7opp.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information or information about their friends, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Personal information includes but is not limited to name, address, phone, email address, school, church, clubs, etc. 

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. 

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated. 

Contacting Us.

We can be contacted through our online support desk at:

www.DanBCauthron.net
